[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the famous quote from Rene Descartes that means I think, therefore I am.", "correct_answer": "Cogito, ergo sum", "incorrect_answers": ["Omnia, vincit amor", "Vivere est cogitare", "Vincit omnia veritas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What award was given to President George W. Bush in 2004?", "correct_answer": "The Raspberry Award for worst leading actor", "incorrect_answers": ["The Stillman Award for Leadership", "The Hendley Award for Great Americans", "The Thurbridge Award  for Freedom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would be from the North American continent?", "correct_answer": "79", "incorrect_answers": ["152", "224", "363"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is is the only strictly-marine herbivorous mammal in the world?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Dugong", "Sea pig", "Sea cow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This plant, native to the shallow waters of the Amazon River basin, is the largest representative of waterlilies.", "correct_answer": "Victoria waterlily", "incorrect_answers": ["American Lotus", "Sacred Lotus", "Red lily"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What college is Baby planning to attend in the movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Mt. Holyoke", "incorrect_answers": ["Yale", "Harvard", "Notre Dame"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A baby cobra is fully able to defend itself in as little as this many hours after being born.", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "48", "72"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor was offered the part of Special Agent Dave Kujan in the 1995 movie The Usual Suspects, but he turned it down.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Christopher Walken", "Al Pacino", "Robert De Niro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the  word geometry mean?", "correct_answer": "earth measure", "incorrect_answers": ["width and length", "shapes and sizes", "size and measurement"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor/actress who starred in the film The Poseidon Adventure appeared in the TV series The Hardy Boys/Nancy Drew Mysteries?", "correct_answer": "Pamela Sue Martin", "incorrect_answers": ["Pamela Sue Anderson", "Roddy McDowell", "David Cassidy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ganache is a fancy word for an apron.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of plasmodium?", "correct_answer": "The parasite that causes malaria", "incorrect_answers": ["The part of the blood that covers red and white blood cells and platelets", "The liquid-like substance found in animal and plant cells", "The gel-like substance that holds fish eggs together"]}]